Michael Brodis

B.S Computer Science (est. 2022) 3.73 GPA

www.michaelbrodis.com

303-210-5016

Michael@michaelbrodis.com

SKILLS

C, C++, HTML5, CSS, Linux, Git, OOP, Java, Team Leadership, Critical Thinking, Android Programing, Microsoft Visual Studio

Projects

Personal Website www.michaelbrodis.com

• Using modern HTML5 and CSS i created an aesthetic personal website

Android Quizlet app Android Studio / Java

 I made a simple quiz app using Android studio, modern Java, MVC project design, and event based programing

Minecraft court Plugin Spigot Framework / Java

I made a plugin for a minecraft server that I was the lead dev on. The
plugin interacted with the minecraft spigot framework to give the
experience of a legal court.

EXPERIENCE

Campus IT Support, - Andrews University

August 2020 - Present

Mcdonalds, - Guest Experience Lead

May 2019 - August 2019

EDUCATION

Andrews University, Berrien Springs Michigan - B.S. Computer

Science 3.73 GPA

August 2019 - December 2022 (est)